**We're sorry.** CNA.com uses Javascript to ensure the best possible experience. For optimal viewing of this site, or to submit information through a form, please ensure that Javascript is enabled for your web browser. You may be required to close and reopen your browser.

* [Pay My Bill](javascript:void(0);)

[](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/home)[Industries](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/industries/all) [Products & Solutions](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/products/all) [Risk Control](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/risk-control) [Claims Center](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/claims-center) [Find an Agent](javascript:void(0);) [Agent Login](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/agentcenter)

Industries

We provide deep expertise, attentive service and tailored business insurance solutions to help manage exposures and minimize loss across a wide array of industries.

Products  
& Solutions

Our wide range of business insurance products and solutions are specialized to meet the insurance and risk management needs of any business around the world.

Products

Solutions

Risk Control

With an average of more than 20 years of experience, CNA Risk Control professionals drive a program of systematic, sustainable risk control solutions designed to increase productivity and help protect your bottom line.

Tools & Services

Education

Agent Login

Secure logins, public resources - everything you need to quickly get to the information you need.

* [PAY MY BILL](javascript:void(0);)
* [PRODUCTS & SOLUTIONS](javascript:void(0);)

* [Main Navigation](javascript:void(0);)

Industries

We provide deep expertise, attentive service and tailored business insurance solutions to help manage exposures and minimize loss across a wide array of industries.

Products  
& Solutions

Our wide range of business insurance products and solutions are specialized to meet the insurance and risk management needs of any business around the world.

Products

Solutions

Risk Control

With an average of more than 20 years of experience, CNA Risk Control professionals drive a program of systematic, sustainable risk control solutions designed to increase productivity and help protect your bottom line.

Tools & Services

Education

Agent Login

Secure logins, public resources - everything you need to quickly get to the information you need.

* [Affinity Programs](javascript:void(0);)

{}

Web Content Viewer (JSR 286)

Privacy

Privacy Policy
==============

selectCNA Privacy Center Privacy Policy Candidate Privacy Policy

Need more information about managing your business risks?

* * *

Revised: 6/28/2024

CNA and its affiliates (“CNA”, “we”, “our,” or “us”) value your privacy. CNA’s Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to information CNA may have collected from or about you or you have provided to others on our behalf and referred to as “CNA Services” in this Policy.  This policy explains how and why CNA collects, uses, and shares your Personal Information for our business purposes, consistent with applicable laws.  Certain of our products and services are subject to additional privacy requirements set forth in other supplemental policies.  If there is a conflict between this Policy and a supplemental policy, the supplemental policy will apply. This Policy applies to CNA operations in the United States, with certain state-specific privacy requirements applicable to “consumers” as that term is defined under the relevant state law.  If you are looking for additional information related to CNA’s affiliates located outside of the United States, please refer to our jurisdiction section located on CNA Privacy Center’s welcome page. 

* * *

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

“Personal Information" is information that readily identifies you as an individual, as well as other pieces of information that, when combined with your name and other items, can be used to identify you.  The specific Personal Information that CNA collects, uses, and shares relating to you will depend on the nature of CNA's relationship or interaction with you. CNA may collect Personal Information from you, your agents, employers, insureds, medical providers, legal counsel, other individuals or service providers as necessary for a business purpose. The information below sets out the categories of Personal Information CNA may have collected from or about you for a business purpose, in the past 12 months:

**Government Issued Identifiers**

Definition: Identification numbers provided by any government agency.

_Examples_: Social security number, driver’s license number, or state identification number.

**Product or Service-related Information**

Definition: Details provided to support a claim or underwrite an insurance policy.

_Examples_: Demographics, receipts, proof of damage, loss history, or loss exposure.

**Criminal History**

Definition: Information related to criminal activity.   
_Examples_: Convictions or court judgments.

**Internet Network Activity**

Definition: Information related to interactions with our portals, websites, applications, or advertisements.

_Examples_: Browsing history, clickstream data, or search history. 

**Audio and Visuals**

Definition: Recordings of information by audio, video, or picture.

_Examples_: Voicemails, voice recordings, photographs, or videos.

**Contact Information**

Definition: Information used to contact an individual.  
_Examples_: Name, postal address, email address, or telephone number.

**Employment Information**

Definition: Information about previous or current employment.  
_Examples_: Employment history, qualifications, licensing, or disciplinary records.

**Education History**

Definition: Information maintained by an educational institution or party acting for or on behalf of the educational institution.  
_Examples_: Education records or transcripts.

**Financial Information**

Definition: Information related to banking, monetary transactions, and credit.  
_Examples_: Bank account number or credit history.

**Medical and Health Information**

Definition: Information that describes health, medical conditions, or health care or payment.  
_Examples_: Health records, diagnosis, prescriptions, physical or mental health diagnoses or treatment.

Personal Information does not include information that has been made public from federal, state, or local government records. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to CNA or to CNA's service providers, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to do so and to permit CNA to use the information you provide.

**USING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

CNA may use Personal Information to:

* Contact you, or send information you have asked to receive about CNA products and services;
* Process claims you have submitted using CNA Services;
* Service your insurance needs;
* Confirm or correct information you have submitted;
* Personalize your experience while using CNA Services or other digital platforms;
* Contact you for other business reasons;
* Let you participate in sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (see "Promotions, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions" below);
* Inform you of CNA jobs and to decide if you have the skills for a job;
* Protect CNA's privacy and property, as well as the privacy and property of you or others;
* Prevent fraud and other crimes;
* Comply with laws and legal processes, including responding to court, regulatory or governmental requests; and
* As otherwise allowed or required by law.

CNA retains Personal Information only for as long as is reasonably necessary for fulfilment of the disclosed purposes above.

**Sweepstakes, Contests, and Other Promotions**

CNA may sponsor or participate in promotions including contests, sweepstakes or other activities.  To join in a promotion, you may be asked to provide certain Personal Information or other information to CNA or to a third party managing the promotion. This may include the collection and use of Personal Information and other information by a third party. While your participation in any Promotion is purely voluntary, by participating, you agree to the Promotion’s terms, conditions, and official rules of the Promotion.    

**DISCLOSURES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

CNA may disclose your Personal Information to other parties in order to provide you with the services that you have requested from us. In order to provide your requested services, we may disclose your information to:

* CNA’s affiliated companies.
* Third parties that help manage, support, and market CNA's business and deliver CNA Services. Examples of these third parties may include:
    * agents or brokers,
    * claims management service providers,
    * background check service providers,
    * other insurance companies,
    * regulators,
    * administrators,
    * website hosting services,
    * data analysts,
    * payment processors,
    * services that support our computer systems,
    * email delivery services, and
    * external digital platforms to personalize your experience.
* Insurance support groups and consumer reporting agencies.
* Third parties to market their products and services to you if you have given CNA permission to provide your information to them.

* A third party in the event of any acquisition, reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other reassignment of all or part of CNA's business, assets, or stock. This includes disclosure in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings.
* Others, as CNA decides are necessary or appropriate:
    * under applicable law, including laws outside your country or territory of residence,
    * to comply with legal processes,
    * to respond to requests from public, governmental, and regulatory authorities, including such requests initiated outside of your country or territory of residence,
    * to enforce CNA's Terms and Use,
    * to protect CNA's operations,
    * to protect CNA's rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of you or others,
    * to detect and prevent fraud, and
    * to allow CNA to pursue fixes or limit damages CNA may sustain.
* Others, as otherwise allowed by law.

While CNA may disclose Personal Information to affiliated entities and third parties as specified above, CNA does not sell Personal Information and does not share your Personal Information with third parties for the purpose of targeted advertising.

**STATE-SPECIFIC PRIVACY STATEMENTS**

Notice to California Residents

Consumers who reside in California have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. For the purpose of this section, “consumer” includes individual consumers, as well as employees, job applicants, and individuals acting in their professional capacity. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed;
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information;
* The right to opt-out of the sale or sharing (for targeted advertising) of your Personal Information;
* The right to object to specific forms of processing of your data; and
* The right to request a manual review of an automated decision.

While CNA may collect certain Sensitive Personal Information about consumers, we limit the use of the consumer’s Sensitive Personal Information for our business purposes.

Notice to Colorado Residents

Consumers who reside in Colorado have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed;
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information; and
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling.

Notice to Connecticut Residents

Consumers who reside in Connecticut have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed;
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information;
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling; and
* If you provide us with Personal Information that we use in automated decision-making, you have the right to obtain a copy of that Personal Information in a convenient and shareable format.

Notice to Oregon Residents

Consumers who reside in Oregon have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed;
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information; and
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling.

Notice to Texas Residents

Consumers who reside in Texas have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information; and
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling.

Notice to Utah Residents

Consumers who reside in Virginia have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights: 

* The right to know what information of yours is collected and how it is processed; 
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with; 
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA; 
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information; 
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information; 
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling; and
* If you provide us with Personal Information that we use in automated decision-making, you have the right to obtain a copy of that Personal Information in a convenient and shareable format. 

Notice to Virginia Residents

Consumers who reside in Virginia have certain additional rights regarding their Personal Information. These rights relate to the use and collection of Personal Information by CNA, and may include one or more of the following rights:

* The right to know what information of yours is processed and how it is processed;
* The right to know who CNA shares your information with;
* The right to access your Personal Information maintained by CNA;
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information;
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information;
* The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, the sharing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, or the use of your Personal Information for profiling; and 
* If you provide us with Personal Information that we use in automated decision-making, you have the right to obtain a copy of that Personal Information in a convenient and shareable format.

**HOW TO MAKE A PRIVACY RIGHTS REQUEST**

You may make a request to exercise any of your privacy rights described in the Additional Privacy Statements section above, using either of the following methods: 

Email: [CNAPrivacyOffice@cna.com](mailto:CNAPrivacyOffice@cna.com), or  
Calling, toll-free: 877-246-2902.

When making a privacy rights request, you will need to provide certain identifying information to allow us to verify the request and locate your information. We will evaluate and process your request subject to exceptions as outlined by applicable law. CNA will not discriminate or retaliate against you for exercising your privacy rights.

**Format of Requested Information**

CNA may deliver the requested information by mail or electronically. If provided electronically, the information will be in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily useable format that allows you to easily transmit this information to another entity.

**Fees**

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive or repetitive. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request. 

**Reconsideration**

If you are concerned that we might have violated your privacy rights, or you disagree with a decision we made about your individual rights, you may use the contact information listed at the end of this notice to ask us to reconsider your request.  We will evaluate and process your reconsideration request in accordance with applicable law. 

**COOKIE STATEMENT**

CNA and its service providers may collect Cookies. A cookie is a piece of information stored on the device you are using to access the CNA Services. CNA uses cookies for security purposes and to:

* Help navigation,
* Improve the design and features of the CNA Services,
* Better provide information, and
* Personalize your experience while using the CNA Services and/or other digital platforms

Cookies also let CNA select which of CNA's advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you. These are then displayed while you are using the CNA Services and/or other digital platforms. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser lets you decline using cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may then be asked to re-enter certain information each time you visit the CNA Services. You may also lose some useful features such as personalization and “keep me signed in” and “remember me”.

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES AND WEBSITES**

CNA Services may sometimes include links to third party websites. This Policy does not apply to any information, including Personal Information, you provide to third party websites. CNA is not responsible for the privacy or other practices, including security practices, of any third-party website.

CNA’s social media platforms may use services such as Facebook, LinkedIn, and Twitter. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any social media platform provider.

A link to a third-party website within CNA Services does not mean CNA endorses these websites or the services they offer.

**SAFEGUARDING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

CNA Services uses reasonable safeguards to protect your Personal Information. However, information transmission and storage systems are not 100% secure. Please contact us immediately at the following number if you believe your Personal Information has been exposed:  Global Security Operations Center: (866) 262-6244.

**Social Security Protection Statement**

CNA protects social security numbers through the use of physical, electronic, and procedural safety measures. We also limit which members of our workforce may access social security numbers.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

CNA Services are not intended for use by minors, including children under the age of thirteen. CNA does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children.

**CORRECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you want to correct the Personal Information that CNA has collected about you through this Policy, please contact CNA’s Privacy Office using the contact information set forth at the end of this Policy.

**OTHER INFORMATION**

 **“Do Not Track” Signals**

CNA Services do not respond to “do not track” signals.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

CNA reserves the right to change this Policy at any time. The "revised" legend at the top of this web page shows when the last revision was made. Any changes become active upon notice being provided. Notice of changes may be given by any reasonable means including by posting a notice on the CNA Website. Your use of CNA Services after changes to this Policy means that you accept the terms of the revised Policy.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have questions or want more information about this Policy, please contact CNA’s Privacy Office by: 

Email: [CNAPrivacyOffice@cna.com,](mailto:CNAPrivacyOffice@cna.com) or

Phone: 877-246-2902 (toll-free).

cnacontent/SA-CNAcom/SA-FatFooter/SA-Privacy/privacy-policy/CT-PrivacytDefaultContent Privacy Default Content

hiddenheader

**IMPORTANT NOTICE:** CNA would like to place cookies on your computer to improve your use of this website. To learn more, see our [Privacy Center](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/privacy/privacy-center).  
By continuing to use this website you shall be deemed to have consented to our use of cookies and to have accepted our website [Privacy Policy](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/privacy/privacy-policy#04).

Continue >>

/web/guest/cna/cnaform/!ut/p/b1/04\_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2M3Z3cDBwdHT2DAv1cDQ0sDPQLsh0VAfaYoTo!/?nID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cnaSoloMode=true

/web/guest/cna/ClaimForms/!ut/p/b1/04\_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2CDLyNDBxdDbwD3ICku6epfkG2oyIA-fqI7Q!!/?nID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cnaSoloMode=true

 United States - English

* [](https://twitter.com/cna_insurance "Go to CNA's X (formerly Twitter) website in a new window")

By visiting our web site,you accept the terms and conditions as described in our [Terms of Use](https://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/cnadisclaimer/termsofuse).

"CNA" is a service mark registered by CNA Financial Corporation with the United States Patent and Trademark Office. Certain CNA Financial Corporation subsidiaries use the "CNA" service mark in connection with insurance underwriting and claims activities. Copyright © CNA. All rights reserved.

Please wait...

/web/guest/cna/findanagent/!ut/p/b1/04\_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2c\_DwNDRz9\_YGEn6mBr5mhvp9-QbajIgAyUYsY/?nID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cID=Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022&cnaSoloMode=true

/web/wcm/connect/f9cb0d27-635b-44bd-84ff-39a2438fba6d/FAAgent\_overlay\_prod.png?MOD=AJPERES /web/wcm/connect/85785d5f-e0ec-4f69-9314-05de5913a751/Find-an-agent-large+1024+X+175.jpg?MOD=AJPERES

/web/guest/cna/privacy Privacy Policy | CNA Z6\_40KKTL4U2B7EA0QDELG95H2022 /CNA /Privacy | CNA
